{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_10_30X13H",
                "player_15_30X13H",
                "player_1_30X13H",
                "player_6_30X13H"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                10,
                15,
                1,
                6
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -2685.178,
                    -75.112,
                    228.4,
                    0,
                    93.96609680019907,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2436.446,
                    -114.339,
                    228.525,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -2931.064,
                    -412.678,
                    228.18,
                    0,
                    59.30039130313074,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2973.995,
                    17.299,
                    228.058,
                    0,
                    -9.011982906341728,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_30X13H"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -2641.843,
                    -141.708,
                    428.4,
                    0,
                    116.78475315108483,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -2414.096,
            -415.913,
            228.213
        ],
        "sample_radius": 907.9262328590457
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -3353.186,
            42.584,
            228.058,
            0,
            -16.872810893538087,
            0
        ],
        [
            -2085.232,
            -265.244,
            234.497,
            0,
            169.5214423714047,
            0
        ],
        [
            -2787.762,
            -660.74,
            253.622,
            0,
            84.01290008036909,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is farther from the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, White_Drone or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is farther from the_woman_in_black_vest, White_Drone or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, White_Drone or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans in the scene are currently in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "One"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are wearing glasses in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many humans are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many male individuals in the scene have light skin?",
                "answer": "One"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many humans are observed in either a 'stand' or 'holding something' posture?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals who are not bald are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "Three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the maroon polo shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in the brown sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. holding an object",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. waving"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing sunglasses and a dark green shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. standing",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. standing"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black tactical vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. jumping",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouching"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. In front of"
            }
        }
    }
}